Contact

alofay504@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andrea-lofay-msn-arnp-np-c-351032175 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Patient Safety

Certifications

SANE

PICC

Andrea Lofay, MSN, ARNP, NP-C

Nurse Practitioner

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Summary

Compassionate nurse with over fifteen years of service in the healthcare field. Offers a unique perspective on problem-solving and team building as an Advanced Practice Nurse and dedicated partner in the healthcare system. Has performed many roles within the healthcare system that has allowed growth and development in leadership and critical thinking. Possesses a strong desire to learn and grow within an established organization and be part of healthcare team that invests in their employees. Seeks to provide the highest level of care based on the most up-to-date evidence based practice.

Experience

Florida Vein Center Nurse Practitioner March 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Bradenton, Florida

BayCare Health System
Registered Nurse
February 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Medical Solutions
Travel Nurse
2015 - February 2016 (1 year)

Emergency Department

Blanchard Valley Health System 2 years 5 months

Registered Nurse February 2013 - June 2015 (2 years 5 months) Findlay, Ohio Registered Nurse February 2013 - June 2015 (2 years 5 months) Findlay, Ohio

Education

Chamberlain University

Master's degree, Nurse Practitioner